分隔的世界
Worlds so far apart
被遗忘的心
hearts hung out to dry
我仍想问好
They'll have my regards
只望有时间
just wish we had time
已经过太久
It's been much too long
自从上次见
since I've their eyes
放手的念头
Trying to let go
我从未想过
was never on my mind
但谁能从，谎言中分出现实
But who can tell lies from reality
当每个人看法一致？
when everyone sees the same?
谁又能够，写下银河的每一哩
And who can spell out
the miles of the galaxies
当它就是太多空间？
when there's just too much space?
而它就是太多空间
And there's just too much space
听好你字句
Listen to your words
否则就成玩物
or they will pass you by
每个人听见
Everyone who heard
都会看穿谎言
will see right through your lies
想像自己与星群，飘在太空中
It's not hard to imagine
yourself out in space
的确很简单
floating with the stars
但当真的发生时，
But with everything that happens,
在那处境下
happening all around you
你也不再是你
It's just not who you are
但谁能从，谎言中分出现实
But who can tell lies from reality
当每个人看法一致？
when everyone sees the same?
谁又能够，写下银河的每一哩
And who can spell out
the miles of the galaxies
当它就是太多空间？
when there's just too much space?
而它就是太多空间
And there's just too much space
你是否会屏弃你所知一切？
Would you turn your back
on everything you know?
并且不往回看，并且不知道去向？
and not look back,
and not know where to go?
分隔的世界
Worlds so far apart
被遗忘的心
hearts hung out to dry
我仍想问好
They'll have my regards
他们一直在心上
they're always on my mind
但谁能从，谎言中分出现实
But who can tell lies from reality
当每个人看法一致？
when everyone sees the same?
谁又能够，写下银河的每一哩
And who can spell out
the miles of the galaxies
当它就是太多空间？
when there's just too much space?
而它就是太多空间
And there's just too much space